quoteswave.com 2015-06-03

# Privacy Policy | Quoteswave

* This privacy policy sets out how **QuotesWave** uses and protects any information that you give search Quates when you use this website. QuotesWave is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. QuotesWave may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from September 7, 2011.

 **How we use cookies**

– A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

– We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

– Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

– You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

 **Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. These companies may use some information (such as your domain type, your IP address, about your visits to this and other Websites) in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Google, one of our third-party advertisers, may add a cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. To find out more about Google and its DoubleClick DART cookie used to generate interest-based advertising, or to opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google Ad Content Network Privacy Policy"). Your use of this website without opting out means that you understand and agree to data collection to provide you with interest-based advertising.

 **Use of IP Addresses**

An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are browsing the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website, analyze trends, track users’ movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the website. An IP address does not contain any personally identifiable information.

 **Links to other websites**

QuotesWave is not responsible for the content or practices of third party websites that may be linked to our Sites. Our Sites may link to websites operated by other companies; we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites. Visitors to these web sites should refer to each web site’s respective privacy policies and practices.

 **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [email](http://www.quoteswave.com/contact "Contact Email") us.  
**  
**
